utrader.com 2015-05-27

# Privacy Policy

AUDJPY

73.74000 / 73.74300

XAUUSD

1662.840 / 1662.960

Privacy Policy

The purpose of the uTrader (known herein as “we, our or us”) Privacy Policy is to inform traders (known herein as “you”) of our procedures and policies regarding the collection disclosure and use of any personal information that is gathered when you visit our uTrader.com site (herein known as “site”) or when you access our site via our mobile application (herein known as “service”).

We reserve the right to change or amend this policy at any time. If material changes are made to this policy, we will modify this policy to reflect the changes as well as post a notice regarding the changes on our website. For this reason, we recommend that you regularly consult this policy.

This policy is a crucial part of the General Terms and Conditions (known herein as “Terms and Conditions”) for our site.

_**Information Collection**_

**Personally Identifiable Information**

During use of our Service, we will ask for specific personally identifiable information which will be used to identify you, contact you and administer your account (known herein as “Personal Information”). This information will also be used to allow you to access some restricted parts of the Site and Service. The Personal information we request may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and your bank account or credit card details. We may maintain information regarding your trading activity in addition to monitoring and recording some or all of the communications between you and uTrader. Some links on the Site may also allow us to track which of these links have been followed by you.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We will collect the following information when you use our Service and/or Site:

Information that is collected by your browser anytime you visit a website (known herein as “Log Data”). The Log Data that we maintain can include, but is not limited to, your computer’s browser type, Internet Protocol address, the previous page you visited and the information which you search for on the Site and while using the Service. With your consent, we may also maintain a PushID and Mobile IP if you use a mobile device to access the Service.

We use “cookies” just like other websites do. A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your computer’s hard disk which enables record-keeping. “Persistent cookies” are used to save your username and password for future times when you log into the Site. “Session ID cookies” are used to enable specific features of the Service and to help us understand how you use the Service. This type of cookie also monitors web traffic routing on the site and aggregate usage of the Service. By changing your browser’s options you can instruct it to prompt you before accepting cookies from websites or stop it from accepting cookies all together. However, you may not be able to access all aspects of the Site or Service if you choose not to accept cookies.

We use a web analytics service to help us obtain information regarding the use of the Site. It is provided by Google, Inc (herein known as “Google”). The cookie generates information about how you use the Site and your IP address and this information can be stored by Google on its servers. Google then uses this information to compile reports on website activities for the website operators plus providing the operators with additional services which have to do with internet usage and website activity. Google may transfer the information it gathers to third parties if required by the law or to other third parties which process information on Google’s behalf. You have the right to refuse the cookies by setting this option on your browser however doing so may limit your use of the full functionality of the website. By choosing to use the Site, you are consenting to allow Google to process data about you for the purposes described above.

_**Third Party Sites**_

This Policy only applies to the Service. We have no control over other websites, services or applications that provide information, advertisements, over banners or links from within the Site or Service. These third party websites, services or applications may use their own cookies or place other files on your hard disk. Subject to the third party’s own privacy policy, personal data may be collected. We recommend that you read any third party privacy policies listed on their websites, services or applications before using them.

_**How We Use Information**_

Personal Information can be used for any of the following purposes: (i) to provide the Service, (ii)to personalize your experience, (iii) to administer use of the Service plus all accounts you have with us, (iv) to provide you with offers from us that you may find useful including promotional materials, marketing materials or newsletter, (v) to inform you of service announcements, (vi) to enforce out Terms of Use, (vii) to contact you for the purposes of obtaining feedback regarding the Service and the Site, (viii) on behalf of a third party, and (ix) to resolve disputes between users of the Service or the Site and users and us. In the event that you do not wish to receive offers, announcements or information, you can unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions listed on the communication materials.

Non-Personal Information will be used for the purposes stated above and for the purpose of (i) improving the Service and the Site, (ii) review and examine use of the Service and the Site (iii) to monitor the technical administration of the Service and the Site, (iv) confirm that users meet the required criteria to have their requests processed, and (v) to generate data regarding the behavior of users as related to characteristics, interests, the website and the Service.

**Personal and Non-Personal Information may also be used for:**

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. No personal information will be included when we share aggregate information including offers and queries which are generated when using the Service including Log Data and non-identifying information. Third parties can use this information for demographic profiling, industry analysis, to send specific targeted advertising for services and products or for additional commercial purposes.

Combined Information. Certain Non-personal Information and Personal Information may be combined in order to provide you with services and information tailored to your preferences and to personalize and improve the Services and Site. If any of your Personal Information is linked with other information, the combined information will be treated solely as Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.

Service Providers. Third party companies may be employed to facilitate to provide the Service on our behalf. They may also preform administrative services for the Site and the Service including, but not limited to, administration, maintenance, payment processing, web analytics and hosting and database management services. Personal Information may be accessed by these third party companies in order to perform tasks. These companies are obligated to follow the guidelines of this Policy.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We cooperate with law enforcement officials, governments and private parties to comply with and enforce the law. As we believe necessary, and at our sole discretion, we will release any information about you to law enforcement or government agencies when we need to respond to legal processes and claims to protect a person’s safety or public safety, to protect our property and rights as well as those of our third parties’ or to stop and prevent activitie that we consider to be or to pose a risk to being unethical, inappropriate, illegal or legally actionable.

Business Transfers. In the case of a merger, reorganization, sale, acquisition of some or all of our assets or in the event of our bankruptcy, we may transfer, sell or share your Log Data and Personal information among other information.

With respect to certain services, we may also post additional ancillary privacy notices.

_**Changing or Deleting Your Information**_

Our users are welcome to review, correct, update or deled their Personal information as long as it is not being retained for legitimate business purposes or by law. If you choose to delete all such information, we may deactivate your account. According to our policies in effect at the time, we may remove any information related to you or provided by you.

_**Security**_

Safeguarding your information is a concern to us, and, to this effect, we protect your information from unauthorized disclosures and access using a variety of measures. However, we cannot promise that your private communications or Personal Information will be protected.

Do not ever reply to an email which asks you to update any of your Personal information and contact our customer service department at [support@utrader.com](mailto:support@uTrader.com).

_**International Processing or Transfers**_

Your information can be processed, transferred or maintained outside of your country in a place where privacy laws may not be as strict.

_**Contacting Us**_

Please contact us at [support@uTrader.com](mailto:support@uTrader.com) if you have any questions or concerns about this Policy.
